[Hit x4]
[Gunshots...]
[Hit!]
[Song: "Dangerous"]
The way she came into the place, I knew right then and there...
There was something different about this girl.
[Hit!]
The way she moved, her hair, her face, her lines,
...divinity in motion.
[Hit!]
As she stalked the room,
I could feel the aura of her presence.
Every head turned, feeling passion and lust.
The girl was persuasive. The girl I could not trust.
The girl was bad...
(Others) The girl was dangerous.
[Hit x5]
Hoo!
[Hit!]
Huh x7
She came at me in sections, with the eyes of desire.
I felt trapped into her web of sin.
[Hit!]
A touch, a kiss,
...a whisper of love.
I was at the point of no return.
Deep in the darkness of passion's insanity.
I felt taken by lust's strange inhumanity.
[Hit!]
...was persuasive. This girl I could not trust.
The girl was bad...
(Others) The girl was dangerous.
[Gunshot!]
Huh x2
[Hit!]
Huh x4
[Song: "Smooth Criminal"]
You've been hit by...
You've been struck by...
A smooth criminal.
Aw!
[Hit.]
[Hit x5]
You know you want me~
[Song: "Dangerous"]
Dangerous!
The girl is so dangerous.
Take away my money, throw away my time.
You can call me honey, but you're no damn good for me.
Dangerous!
The girl is so dangerous.
I have to pray to god, cuz I know how lust can blind.
It's a passion in my soul...
But you're no damn lover friend of mine.
[Hit!]
My baby!
You bet, you bet, no, you don't, you don't, don't,
...that's my baby!
(MJ) Dangerous!
(Others) Dangerous!
[Hit!]
(MJ) Dangerous!
(Others) Dangerous!
(MJ) You don't, you don't, don't,
[Hit!]
(MJ) Dangerous!
(Others) Dangerous!
[Hit!]
(MJ) Dangerous!
(Others) Dangerous!
[Hit!]
DJ! DJ!
Woo~
[Hit!]
Get the point?
Good.
Let's dance!
[Hit!]
DJ, now, DJ, DJ,